原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     杏仁斯嘉丽   吃冰棒   肉松
翻译     joy_bwl   Eunice   十月
校对     喃喃
时间轴     风吹来的那片云
后期     蜡笔小新的眉毛
总监     喃喃
姓名
Name?
詹姆斯·麦吉尔
James McGill.
带卡了吗
Bring your card?
带了
Yeah.
在这签字
Sign there.
我能先读一遍吗
Can I read it first?
就是个免责声明而已
It's just a waiver.
你要是受伤了  我们概不负责
We're not responsible if you hurt yourself.
社区服务免责声明
早上好  索尔·古德曼制作公司
Good morning. Saul Goodman Productions.
没错
T-that's right.
我们提供一条龙服务  写策划  拍摄
We, uh -- we do it all -- we write it, shoot it,
安排广告播出  费用非常低廉
get ya on the air for one low, low price.
请问你们是做什么生意的
May I ask what business you have?
修电脑
Computer repair?
这一行在电视上打广告再合适不过了
That is a perfect business to advertise on television
因为电脑是我们的未来
because, you know, computers are our future.
我们的报价
Yes, well, our rates are --
抱歉  我们有辆卡车刚刚开过去
Sorry. That was, uh, one of our trucks.
我们今天拍外景
We're, uh, location shooting today.
大手笔大制作
It's a big production, actually.
通常价格是一支广告一次播放
Our usual rate is one commercial, one airing --
八百五十块钱  但你很幸运
$850, but you're in luck --
我们今天打特价  仅此一次
today, we have a one-time special.
精英套餐
Our Elite package.
七支广告  七次播送
Seven commercials, seven airings for forty --
四千六百块
forty-six hundred dollars.
对  四千六百块
Yeah. Forty-six hundred dollars.
我们还可以  喂
And we can a-- Hello.
喂
Hello?
我没有  因为你一直让我等
No, I didn't, because you keep putting me on hold.
好  我的情...  喂
Okay, my situ-- Hello?
我的情况是这样的
My sit-- Yes, my situation is this.
两个月前  我买了一整年的
I -- Two months ago, I paid for a full year,
但因为一些意外
but, due to unforeseen circumstances,
接下来的十二个月我都没法做律师了
I'm not gonna be a lawyer for the next 12 months.
对  我被停业了
Yes, suspended.
我不做律师工作了
So I'm not practicing,
所以用不着职业过失保险了
so I don't need malpractice insurance,
我想谈谈退款的问题
and I'd like to speak to someone about a refund.
但  那我能不能
But y-- Well, then, may I please speak to someone
跟说了算的人谈谈
who can make a decision?
不不不  别再让我等了  求你了
No, no, no. Don't put me on hold again, please.
喂  喂
He-- hello? He--
等等  这上面写三十分钟
Wait a minute. This says 30 minutes.
对
Yep.
但我们在这干了四个小时
We were out here for four hours.
你一直在打电话
You were on your phone.
你报名的时候就清楚规矩了
You knew the rules when you signed up.
但我比他们捡的垃圾都多
But I collected more garbage than anybody out here.
我为了糊口  必须得开展业务
I have to be able to conduct business to earn a living.
不行
No.
"不行"是什么意思
What do you mean "No"?
你应该把社区服务当成狱中生活
Think of community service as your jail time.
监狱里不让打手机
No phones allowed in jail.
你等等  哥们
W-w-well, hold on there, buddy.
你以为自己是谁啊
I mean, who do you think you are, huh?
你以为你能这么对我们吗
Y-y-you think you can treat us like this?
我们是为了让伟大的
We're out here for the good
阿尔布开克变得更好才来的  不是为了你
of the great city ‭of Albuquerque -- not for you.
你又不是我们的主子
You're not our lord and master.
你不能对我们颐气指使
You don't get to sit back
定夺谁好谁不好
and decide who's worthy and who isn't.
我说得对吗
Am I right?
哥们  你到底上不上车
Dude, are you gonna get in the van or what?
拜托  三十分钟  这可不对
C'mon. 30 minutes? That stuff's not right.
给我多写点吧
You can do better than that.
也可以写个零
We could make it zero.
绝命律师
第三季  第七集
阿尔布开克公园管理局
快点  快点
Come on. Come on!
拜托  宝贝
Come on, baby!
好了
Yes!
快坐上公爵城休闲椅
So come on down to Duke City Recliners
把脚抬起来[好好放松放松]
and put your feet up!
首次购买时提到本广告可打九折
Mention this ad and get 10% off your first purchase.
停
And...cut.
真棒  怎么样
Great! How wathat?
-画面没问题  -声音不错
- Good for camera. - Sound was good.
谢谢  演得不错  等等
Thank you. That was great. Hold up. Hold up.
我要再拍一条
I wanna do one more.
刚才那条可以吗
Was that okay?
挺不错的  但是我  我想
It was great, uh, but I just -- I want --
我想让你能更抓住观众
I want you to connect more with the audience.
就像是在跟朋友说话一样
Like you're talking to a friend.
眼睛盯着镜头  心里想着一个朋友
Look into that lens and see a friend.
能做到吗
Can you do that?
想一个特定的朋友
I mean, think of a specific friend.
-你能看见他吗  -能
- Do you see him? ‭- Yes.
好  他是谁
Okay. Who is he?
-我的朋友罗恩  -好极了
- My friend Ron. ‭- Great.
盯着镜头  想象你看见了罗恩
Look into that lens and see Ron.
你们俩聊着休闲椅
And just two guys, ‭just chattin' about chairs.
别想了
‭D-don't think about it.
放轻松  随意点
‭Just throw it away.
补个妆  准备录音
Last looks. Roll sound.
录音准备好了
Sound speed.
-摄像机  -摄像机准备好了
- Camera? - Cam-camera set.
那么
And...
和你的挚友罗恩聊聊
Havin' a conversation with your good friend Ron.
只是两个人在闲聊
Just a couple of guys talkin'.
你有个关于休闲椅的好消息
And you got some very exciting news about the recliners
迫不及待要跟他分享
that you've been dyin' to share with him.
开拍
And...action.
快坐上公爵城休闲椅
So come on down to Duke City Recliners
把脚抬起来
and put your feet up!
首次购买时提到本广告可打九折
Mention this ad and ‭get 10% off your first purchase.
停
And...cut!
太棒了  这就对了
Great! ‭That's the one!
回放一遍  感觉如何
Check the gate! How did that feel?!
挺好的  你觉得呢
Good, I guess. ‭What -- What did you think?
真棒  太好了
Good! So good!
非常  就是很棒
Just very, very... just great!
非常好
It was very nice.
听着  你找到感觉了  朋友
Listen, you are on a roll, my friend.
我们还是趁热打铁吧
I say we strike while the iron is hot.
还记得我们说过的另一个提议吗
Remember that other offer we discussed?
按优惠价多拍几条广告
More commercials at the discounted rate?
剧组人员都在这
Got my whole crew here.
我们可以再连录七条
We could bang out seven more
让你有机会家喻户晓
and give you a run that'll make you a household name.
-怎么样  -但古德曼先生  我
- Waddya say? - But, Mr. Goodman, I...
觉得再拍几支广告这主意不错
love the idea of more commercials,
但是我做不到
but I just can't swing it.
我妻子不想让我拍这个
My wife didn't want me to do this one.
知道吗
You know what?
常言道  花了钱才有动力赚钱
They say you gotta spend money to make money.
还有
And, uh...
跟你讲  你有个机会
And I tell ya what -- you got a chance here
提高销量  你会增加上百名
to potentially spike your sales by hundreds --
甚至是上千名新顾客
hell, thousands -- of new customers
他们之前可能听都没听说过公爵城休闲椅
who'd never even heard of Duke City Recliners.
你觉得怎么样
What do ya say?
好  好
Sure, s-sure.
但是  但是我说过了
B-But -- But like I said,
我只有做一支广告的钱
I only have enough to pay for the one.
好吧  知道吗
Well, you know what?
我喜欢你  我想帮你
I like you, and I wanna help.
我们刚才说好的打完折
So I know we discussed a discounted rate
每支广告545块
of $545 per commercial,
但如果你现在签下我们的精英套餐
but if you sign up right now for our Elite package --
现在就是七支广告
now, ‭that's seven commercials --
我觉得我们可以给你做到
I think we can do the whole thing for...
每支广告五百块
$500 per commercial.
那就是三千五百块包干
Now, that is $3,500, all in.
这可真是跳楼价了
That is the bargain of a lifetime.
我不知道
I don't know.
你们能赊账吗
Any chance you could do it on credit?
赊账吗
On credit?
不行  不行
No. No.
我没法做
I can't.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
下次吧
Maybe another time.
我先把这支广告的钱给你
Let me get your money for this one.
我们能简单点直接分成四份吗
Can we make this easier and just split it four ways?
"分成四份"  我先把你撕成四块
"Split it four" -- ‭I'll split you four ways.
你们学校没教过你们资本主义吗
Don't they teach you capitalism in that school of yours?
我就是说说  我们也有开销  伙计
I'm just sayin', we got expenses, man.
你...  开...  你们有什么开销
You -- Expen-- You don't have expenses!
花钱的是我  看见这个没
I've got expenses! You see this?
这是我已经花在电视上打广告的钱
This is money I've already spent on airtime for that commercial.
445块
445 bucks.
你知道我还剩多少吗
You know ‭what that leaves me with?
-一百块  -104块9毛5
- $100. - ‭$104.95!
我还得写文案  导演  制作  推广
For writing, directing, producing, client outreach,
销售  交通  都是我干的
sales, transpo -- all of it!
-知道了  -好
- I get it. ‭- Yeah.
公爵城休闲椅
你快点回剪辑室把这个弄完
So let's get you in the editing room and finish this thing,
我不想再听见你们提花销的事了
and I don't want to hear another word about expenses.
好吧  电费
Okay. Electric.
这个月是我付的
‭I paid this month.
还有吗
Anything else?
我买了几令打印纸
I bought a couple reams of paper for the printer.
嗯  打印纸
Hmm. Paper.
一百...  六十二
One hundred...sixty-two.
好了  所以...
Okay, so...
这个月我出的钱多些
Looks like puts me ahead this month...
3172块
$3,172.
好吧  我那份是多少钱
All right. And what's it to even me up?
除以二...
Uh...Divided by 2.
1586块
$1,586.
好吧
Okay.
一千...
One thousand...
五百...
five hundred...
大款先生啊
Mr. Moneybags, huh?
所以这个...
So this...
广告生意
commercial thing.
有赚钱吗
It's turning a profit?
电视呢
It's TV.
怎么可能不赚钱
How could there not be a profit?
你没有...
You didn't...
把你的老本都花光了吧
drain your bank account, did you?
什么  没有  我没...
What? No, I didn't --
那是  中国菜外卖
Uh, oh, that's, uh, Chinese food.
我给我们俩点的
I ordered it for us.
你今晚要加班  对吗
You're workin' late, right?
对  谢谢
Yeah. Right. Thanks. Oh, uh...
等下  给你
Wait, here.
不了  我请
No, I got this.
-你好  -二十四块
- Hey, hi. ‭- $24.
给  不用找了
Here. Keep the change.
就一块钱吗
A dollar?
对啊
Yeah.
总比没有强
We can make it zero.
天呐  怎么回事
Geez! What the hell?!
搞什么鬼
I mean, what the hell?
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
放松
Relax.
我只想和你聊聊
I just want to talk.
聊聊
Talk?
你是说你要跟我道歉吗
‭You mean, like, apologize?
因为我现在只想听你道歉
'Cause that's really the only talk I want to hear.
我想做笔交易
I want to do some business.
和以前一样
Like before.
交易
Business?
这是偷走我棒球卡的暗号吗
Is that, like, code ‭for stealing my baseball cards?
我不是来找你要棒球卡的
I'm not here for your baseball cards.
我来...
I'm here...
是为了这个
for this.
你能搞到更多吗
Can you get more of these?
你想我去偷这个吗
You want me to steal this?
开个处方然后到药店去
Get a prescription and go to a pharmacist.
-很便宜的  -我要的是空胶囊
- It'll be cheap. - ‭I need those capsules empty...
里面会灌上别的东西
before they're sealed.
上面带着那种特殊的标记
With those exact markings.
我工作的地方不产这个
Well...the place I work doesn't make these.
但是...
But...
但是什么
But what?
我也许可以说研究需要搞一些样品
I could probably ‭get some samples diverted on an R&D request.
那就这么办
So do it.
为什么  这有什么用
Why? ‭I mean, what's the point?
我要
I need them. ‭
好吧
O-kay.
如果我不呢
And if I don't get them?
你要怎么样
Then what?
你要威胁我吗
Are you gonna threaten me?
打断我的腿
Break my legs?
你帮我弄到这些药
You get me those pills,
我给你两万
and I'm gonna pay you $20,000.
去弄
Get them.
把球给她
Let her have the ball.
等下  好吗
Hold on, okay?
爸
Hey, Pop.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
挺好的  进展顺利
Uh, yeah. It's coming along.
有几个志愿者想来帮忙
Have a couple of volunteers here who want to help.
谢了  我一个人弄就行
Well, thanks, but I think I'm good.
拜托  我们不能让你一个人干活
Please, we can't let you do it all by yourself.
而且这些设备还是你出的钱
Certainly not after you bought all the supplies.
至少让教堂补偿一下你
At least let the church reimburse you.
-这是我捐的  -行了
- It's a donation. - C'mon.
我们几个虽然技艺不精但很愿意出力
You've got unskilled but eager laborers.
让我们做点什么吧
Let us do something.
你就告诉我们做什么就行
Just point and tell us what to do.
好吧...
All right, uh...
那你把一袋水泥倒进
How about you dump one of those packs
手推车里
into the wheelbarrow?
你  你把这个桶接满水
And you -- you fill that bucket up to the brim with water.
然后倒进去  一点一点地倒
And then you dump it in, little by little,
你边倒他一边用锄头搅拌
while he stirs it with a hoe.
-交给我  -好的
- You got it. - Okay.
我准备好了  我做什么
I'm ready. What can I do?
我觉得没什么活儿了
I think we're covered.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
不是什么麻烦的活儿
It's not that big a job.
我这样做对吗
Am I doing this right?
你要不试试这个
Why don't you try using this instead?
什么意思
Excuse me?
这是用来修走道的
It's for the walkway.
你看着
Look.
可以留下纹路
It puts down a texture
这样路面湿了  小孩不会滑倒
so the kids don't slip when it gets wet.
这样吗
Like this?
没错
You got it.
动作要轻
Nice and gentle.
你是凯莉的爷爷  对吧
You're Kaylee's Pop-Pop, right?
是的
‭I am.
我就是那位很骄傲的祖父
I am ‭the very proud grandfather.
-我是安妮塔  -麦克
- I'm Anita. ‭- Mike.
-很高兴认识你  麦克  -我也是
- Nice to meet you, Mike. - ‭And you.
谢谢你帮忙
And thanks for helping.
好吧  谢谢你让我帮忙
Well, thank you for not trying to do this all by yourself.
卡尔
Carl?
在
Yeah.
帮我看会儿场子  行吗
Hold the fort ‭for a few minutes, wouldja?
没问题  麦克
You got it, Mike.
你来了
You're here.
你这叫秘密行动吗
This your idea of stealth?
我从没说过我很擅长秘密行动
I never claimed to be good at this.
完全不会
Any of it.
这一点  我倒是同意
On that, we can agree.
是啊  所以我来了
Yeah, I know. That's why I'm here.
我想再次雇你
I wanna hire you again.
干什么
Do what now?
雇你  做我的助手
Hire you. As my back-up man.
待遇和以前一样
Same terms as before.
我不想再犯上次相同的错误
I don't wanna make ‭the same mistake as last time.
你不想犯相同的错误
You don't wanna make the same mistake,
那就不要卷进
then don't get involved
你正准备卷进的任何事情
with whatever it is you're getting involved with.
但
But...
我已经卷进去了
I'm involved already.
但我没有
I'm not.
好吧
Well...
是纳乔·瓦尔加
It's Nacho Varga.
他怎么了
What about him?
他闯入我的房子
He broke into my house.
他在里面等着我
He was inside, waiting for me.
不知道他怎么通过安保系统的
Somehow, he got past my security system.
现在都不知道
I have no idea how!
他只需要拔掉电话线
All he had to do ‭was unplug your phone lines.
是吗
That's it? Huh.
他想要什么
What'd he want?
药
Pills.
其实也不算
Well...not exactly.
空的胶囊
Empty Lydristel capsules.
-什么东西  -就像硝化甘油
- Lydristel? ‭- Yeah. They're like nitroglycerin.
他还给我钱  很多钱
And he offered me money -- lots of money.
远远超过本身的价值
Way more than they're even worth.
但
But...
我怕如果我不做  或者就算我做了
I'm afraid if I don't do it, or even if I do do it...
我不知道
I don't know...
告诉他你无法满足他的需要
Tell him you can't get what he needs.
我已经第订货了
I already ordered them.
货两天就会送到
I mean, the shipment gets here in two days.
他知道
He knows.
那就编个借口
Then make up an excuse.
行  三千块
Fine. $3,000.
我给你三千块
I'll give you $3,000.
我不感兴趣
I'm not interested.
你自己想办法抽身
And you find a way out of it.
但
But --
不感兴趣
Not interested!
计时
听着  我说实话
Look... full disclosure.
当你告诉我们纪律听证会的事时
When you told us about the disciplinary hearing,
我承认  我有担忧
I admit it -- I had concerns.
我要告诉你  我得作尽职调查
So, just so you know, I had to do my due diligence.
我看了听证会文件
I read the transcripts.
全都看了
All of them.
太棒了
It was amazing.
你们对查尔斯做的事
What you did to Charles --
你和詹姆斯完全让他掉进坑里了
You and James set him up perfectly.
你们毁了他
You destroyed him.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我完全无法相信
I couldn't believe some of it.
"我不是疯子  是1216号
"I'm not crazy. It's 1216,
是《大宪章》签署的第二年"
one after Magna Carta."
《大宪章》
The Magna Carta?
太完美了
It was perfect.
"你们觉得这种欺诈很恶劣吗"
"You think this chicanery is bad?"
谁会那么说话
Who talks like that?
第五页显示了各县贷存比的明细
On page 5 is a breakdown of loan-to-deposit ratios by county,
你还能看到
and you can see,
如果梅萨维德银行要遵守第109条
if Mesa Verde is going to comply with Section 109,
你们得提高贷款数额
you will have to raise your loan numbers.
应该搞错了
That can't be right.
我们在亚利桑那州挺好的
We were fine in Arizona.
但联邦存款保险公司在犹他州的要求不同
Yes, but the FDIC requirements in Utah are different.
百分之九十六
96%?
已经那么高了吗
Is it really that high?
我以为亚利桑那州才百分之七十九
I thought Arizona was only 79%.
再说一次  的确如此
Again, it was,
但犹他州有更高的贷存比
but Utah has a higher loan-to-deposit ratio.
我想我们要查一查
I think we're gonna need to check that.
那数字很离谱
That number seems way off.
数字是对的
The numbers are right.
但你可以再看一遍指南
But you can review ‭the guidelines if you want.
就在这儿
Right here.
你是要查一查  还是继续
You gonna check 'em or can we move on?
不了
No...
当然  那就百分之九十六吧
of course. If it's 96%, it's 96%.
我们会增加贷款数额
We'll increase our loan numbers.
没问题
Absolutely.
我们能审核固定抵押贷款利率吗
Can we review ‭these fixed mortgage rates?
因为那绝对是
'Cause that's definitely an area
我们需要关注的领域
we're gonna need ‭to focus our attention --
佩奇  我  刚刚...
Paige, I'm s-- That was...
很不专业
unprofessional.
我不是故意想那么对你说话
I didn't mean ‭to speak to you that way.
金  别担心
Kim. Don't worry.
没问题的  完全没有
It's not a problem. At all.
不  我很抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
我没有理由那么跟你说话
There's no excuse ‭for talking to you like that.
我知道你对这份工作多么认真
I know how hard ‭you've been working on this.
拜托  我已经忘掉了
Please, I've forgotten about it already.
你也应该这么做
You should, too.
行吗
Okay?
在我看来  我们所做的...
As far as I'm concerned, all we did...
我们毁了一个病人
all we did was tear down a sick man.
固定抵押贷款利率
Fixed mortgage rates.
应该是在第三页
I think it's page 3.
-是  -没错
- Yes. - ‭Yeah.
上面有收购对比
There's an acquisition comparison at the top,
如果你想看总额...
and you want to go by total...
上车  没错
Get in! ‭Yeah.
动作快点
Go! Chop-chop!
快  快
C'mon, c'mon!
上车
Get in!
-我们走  -我在挤
- Let's go. - ‭Trying.
这声音不对劲
That doesn't sound good.
快  快
C'mon, c'mon.
我觉得油要满溢了
I think you're flooding it.
-油没有满溢  -你发动过头了
- I'm not flooding it! - You're over-cranking it.
你在说什么鬼话
Oh, you don't know ‭what you're talking about!
无论到不到  我们都要收钱
We're still getting paid whether we get there or not.
或许我们该赶公交车
Maybe we should catch the bus.
得了吧
Come on!
马上就发动了  行吗
Just -- It's gonna start, okay?
油肯定满溢了
Yeah, you definitely flooded it.
-他把电瓶耗没电了  -你把电瓶耗没电了
- He drained the battery. - You drained the battery.
你们能不能不要再说
Can you not talk about something
自己根本不懂的事了
you know absolutely nothing about?
我们可以坐公交车去
There's a bus we could get in.
让我想一下
I just need to think for one minute!
走吧  我们坐公交
Look, ‭we're taking the bus.
好的
Yeah.
摄制组
Film crew!
请等一等
Hold up the bus!
看那个
You see that?
那把芬达吉他  里奇·布莱克摩签名的
Fender Stratocaster, signed by Ritchie Blackmore.
你们知道他是谁吧
You know who that is, right?
谁也没听说过的人
Someone no one's ever heard of?
答得真好
That's real good.
我希望你的父母能乐意
I hope your parents enjoy supporting you
供养你一辈子
for the rest of their lives.
是里奇·布莱克摩啊
C'mon, Ritchie Blackmore.
深紫乐队
Deep Purple.
《墙上的另一块砖》
"Another Brick in the Wall."
未来无望了
I weep for the future.
麦吉尔先生  出了点问题
Mr. McGill, we have a problem.
他们
Them.
伙计们  你们准备好了吗
Hey, fellas. Uh, you ready?
我们已经准备好拍第一镜了
We got the first shot all lined up.
我能跟你们说一下戏吗
Can I walk you through it?
我们也不想这样  但是
We hate to do this to you, but...
我们改变了主意
We're having second thoughts.
我明白了  你们很紧张  有点怯场
I get it. That's just nerves. Just stage fright.
不过没关系  我们有提示牌
Uh, tell you what -- we got cue cards,
还有神奇的剪辑技术  你们看起来会跟
and with the magic of editing, we're gonna make you guys
詹姆斯·加纳和玛丽埃特·哈特利一样上镜
look like James Garner and Mariette Hartley.
不是这个问题
It's not that.
是那个...
It's just that it...
钱有点多..
it seems like too much money...
回报率却不高
For not a whole lot of return.
我的朋友们  这你们可就错了
And that, my friends -- that is where you're mistaken,
这是个品牌意识的问题
because this is about brand awareness.
从现在起  只要人们想起吉它
From now on, ‭when people think guitars,
就会想到"阿尔布开克韵律"
they're gonna think "ABQ In Tune."
想到钢琴  "阿尔布开克韵律"
When they think pianos -- "ABQ In Tune."
还有鼓  木琴
Drums, xylophones...
只需比那把里奇·布莱克摩
For less than the price of that
签名吉它还少的钱
Ritchie Blackmore beauty you got on that rack,
就可以让全城都对"阿尔布开克韵律"念念不忘
you're gonna have the whole town thinking, "ABQ In Tune."
但是播出时段呢
Yeah, but -- but what about the time slot?
《女作家与谋杀案》重播的时段
I mean, ‭"Murder, She Wrote" Repeats?
这时段可不怎么样啊
Come on.
老奶奶们会很愿意为自己的孙子孙女
Grandmas love buying the gift of music
买乐器当作礼物的
for little Johnny and Sally and Skip, hmm?
而且现在是校园音乐季
And it's school-recital season,
孩子们会去哪买录音机呢
so where are the kids gonna get those recorders?
我们不卖录音机
We don't sell recorders.
那就电子合成器
Synthesizers, then.
但重点是  老奶奶们终归是
But the point is, those Social Security checks --
要把她们社保支票花掉的
they got to be spent somewhere.
今天还正好有活动
As it happens, uh, today only,
我可以给你们提供相同的服务  但是
I can, uh, offer the same package, but...
打五折
50% off.
听着
Look...
抱歉  但是不行
I'm sorry, but we can't.
不拍了  伙计们
Not today, guys.
别撤
Don't do that.
朋友们  听我说
Guys. Now, come on.
我知道你们是想拍的
Look, I know you want this.
我知道的  五折啊
I know you do. 50% off!
是的  但我们不那么...
Yeah, we get it, but we're just not...
确定效果
Convinced.
免费
Free.
我免费帮你们拍这条
I'll shoot the spot for free.
免费
For free?
你免费给我们拍
You will shoot this spot for free?
我给你们拍广告  然后负责播出
I'll film your ad, and I'll put it on the air.
但等你们看到这里车水马龙人声鼎沸时
But when you see more traffic coming through here --
一定会的
and you will --
我们就按初始价格再拍其他广告  怎么样
then we do the other spots for the original rate, okay?
这还要拒绝吗
Now, how can you say no?
-他都说到这份上了  -看来没法拒绝了
- I mean, when he puts it like that... - ‭I guess we can't.
很好
Good.
这是你们做的最好的决定
That's the best decision you're gonna make.
最好的
The -- The best!
你要坐公交车吗  麦吉尔先生
You gonna catch the bus, Mr. McGill?
不了  我...
No, I...
你们
You guys...
快去剪辑室吧
get to the editing room.
我要坐一会儿
I just need t-- to sit.
麦吉尔先生
Mr. McGill?
不  我不能拿
No. I-I can't.
没关系
It's okay.
不  这是你的钱
No, that's yours.
你应得的
You earned it.
但你亏钱了
But you're losing money.
不一定
We'll see.
没关系的
It -- It'll be fine.
好吧
Okay.
我终于振作了起来
So, I finally got my act together.
我从柜子里把艾伦的几个箱子拖了出来
I pulled a bunch of Alan's boxes out of the closet.
只不过这花了我八年的时间
Only took me eight years.
我最后洗了一遍艾伦的衣服
I gave all of Alan's clothes a last wash
然后把它们都捐给慈善机构了
before driving them over to Goodwill.
我大哭了一场
I cried.
洗衣服的时候哭
I cried when I washed them.
叠衣服的时候哭
I cried when I folded them.
送走的时候也哭
I cried when I dropped 'em off.
但当我做完这一切时
But once it was done...
感觉好极了
it felt good...
放开这一切
to let them go.
不过我留下了他的制服
I kept his uniform, though.
这个可不能不要
Can't let that go.
我要是把这个也送走  他决不会原谅我
Lord, he'd never forgive me if I let that go.
但是我觉得保留一样东西作纪念没关系
But I figure it's okay to keep one thing, right?
我的意思是
I mean...
别的衣服人们可以穿  但是
people can use the other clothes, but...
一件旧制服对他们有什么用呢
not sure what use they'd have for an old uniform.
我可不记得我在凯莉那么大时
I just don't remember this much homework
有这么多的家庭作业
when I was Kaylee's age.
虽然她觉得没什么  但是...
It doesn't seem to bother her, but still...
大多都是额外作业
Most of it's just busywork.
我们几个家长跟学校谈过
A couple of us actually spoke to the school board,
他们也同意...
and they agreed...
好了  你接吧
Done. All yours.
友情提示  这里咖啡不咋样
Fair warning, ‭the coffee's not all that.
我想如果你能面对这件事
I guess the feel if you can face this,
-你就能面对一切  -可能是吧
- you can face anything. - ‭Could be.
我一定是比自己想像的要坚强
I must be stronger than I think.
介意我问一下吗
You mind if I ask --
-我不是想打探什么  但是  -我猜猜
- and I really don't mean to pry, but -- ‭- Let me guess.
你是有其他的活儿需要我帮忙吗
You have another construction job you need my help on.
不是
Uh, no.
但如果有  我一定第一个找你
But if I do, you'll be the first person I call.
好吧  你问吧
Okay, ask away.
你说你保留了你丈夫的制服
You said you kept your husband's uniform.
他是局里的吗
Was he on the job?
局里
On the job?
你是说警察啊
Oh, you mean the police.
不
No.
艾伦是海军
Alan was a Navy man.
我失去他时  他已经退役了
He was well out of the service when I lost him.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这个小组已经听了很多遍我的故事了
The group has heard my story over and over.
我们就是来干这个的
Well, that's what we're here for.
艾伦喜欢远足
Alan loved to hike.
我们还开了一家野营用品专卖店
We even opened a camping-supply store.
我帮他处理邮购方面的业务
I helped him with ‭the mail-order side of it.
然后
And then, uh...
这是八年前的事了
this was eight years ago --
他去吉拉国家公园爬山
he went hiking in Gila National
就再也没回来
and never came back.
他们找到了我们的车
They found our car,
但始终没找到他
but they never found him.
我不知道
And I don't know if...
他到底是滑倒了  还是心脏病发
he slipped and fell or had a heart attack
又或是遇到了看他不顺眼的恶人
or met someone who didn't like the way he looked...
我完全不知道
I don't know.
即使过了那么多年
And even after all these years,
不知道他的死因  也不知道他的下落...
not knowing how he passed or where he is...
我真希望这些事不会令我在意
I wish it didn't matter.
但我真的放不下
But it does.
喂
Hello?
是我
It's me.
交易做完了吗
You make the deal?
还没有
No. Not yet.
为什么问
Why?
我加入
I'm in.
我们离开这里吧
Hey, let's get outta here.
什么
What?
离开哪里
Get out where?
我正忙着梅萨维德银行的事  我走不开
I am up to my neck in Mesa Verde. I can't.
来  我们这就走
C'mon, we're going.
-不行  -起来
- No, I can't. - ‭Up.
吉米
Jimmy --
不行  你做什么...
Nope. Nothing -- ‭
你做什么都不能阻止我
Nothing you can do to stop this.
有个问题  得由你来开车
Uh, one thing -- you have to drive.
瞧瞧这家伙
Lookit this guy.
就像戴着租来的假发的希区柯克
It's Alfred Hitchcock in a rented toupee.
别闹了
C'mon.
为什么会有人要租假发
Why would you rent a toupee?
从假发店租来的
Y'know, from the Toupee Store.
这样就不用保养假发了
So you don't have to maintain it.
来了  一杯七七
All right. Seven and seven.
太好了
Yeah.
还有一杯古典鸡尾酒
And an Old Fashioned.
继续拿酒来  先生
Keep 'em coming, good sir.
你能不能换刷这张卡
Can you, uh, start charging this card
-别刷那张了  -好的  没问题
- instead of that other one? - Yeah, yeah. You got it.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - No problem.
你不是把卡刷爆了吧
You're not maxing out your cards, are you?
当然不是
Of course not.
我只是  分开来积分
I'm, um, ‭spreading the points around.
我有一套方法
I got a system.
那个蠢材接受了赌注
That moron takes the bet.
他拿了三分  他就是个笨蛋  难道...
He took 3 points. He's a fool. Look, is it wrong...
这边这个家伙
This guy over here.
他想让大家都知道  他出手很大方
Yeah, he wants everyone to know what a big spender he is.
那个人把全副身家都输给我了
I got every dollar the guy owns.
我们是来和一位名人见面的
We're here to meet a celebrity
他要捐钱给我的慈善机构
who's donating to my charity.
凯文·科斯特纳
Kevin Costner.
我去那个角落站着
I-I will go stand in that corner.
你把我指出来  说你要和凯文·科斯特纳见面
You point me out -- you're meeting Kevin Costner.
什么  你长得又不像凯文·科斯特纳
What? You don't look like Kevin Costner.
我长得超像凯文·科斯特纳
I look exactly like Kevin Costner.
总有人走到我面前  跟我说
People are always coming up to me,
他们很喜欢我演的《百万金臂》
saying they loved me in "Bull Durham."
并没有  从没发生过
Never. Never happened.
-经常发生  -一次都没有
- Always. - ‭No, not once.
你过来一下
Hey, you!
-怎么了  先生  -这是什么
- Yes, sir? - ‭What is this?
加了橄榄汁的马天尼
Dirty Martini?
不  这是杯卖十四美金的呕吐物
No, this is a $14 glass of puke.
你还不快点丢掉那副蠢表情
Why don't you get that idiot look off your face
去给我重做一杯
and get me another one?
-那个家伙  -谁提过金酒了
- That guy. - Who said anything about gin?
-我们怎么拿下他  -我要伏特加
- How do we get him? - Well, I want vodka.
怎么  我就这么拿着吗
W-What -- am I just gonna hold it here?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你去给我换一杯
You go and get me another one.
你跟我提过的硬币那招行吗
The -- The trick with the coin you told me about?
我认识你们老板  我是这家店的投资人
I know your boss. I'm an investor here.
-还是假钞那招呢  -不
- Or the counterfeit bill? - ‭No.
我认识你老板  我还认识你老板的老板
I know your boss, and I know your boss' boss.
那家伙是个大混蛋
That guy's a real asshole.
机灵点  去给我弄一杯真正的酒
...act together and get me a real drink.
必须狠狠地收拾他
He needs to go down.Hard.
你这什么卑贱的工作啊
What kind of menial job is this?
我们等会这么做
Here's what we're gonna do.
我们卖给他一张不值钱的信用卡
We're gonna sell him a worthless credit card
以五千美元的价格
for 5,000 bucks.
你要做的是
Here's what you do.
和他眼神接触
Make eye contact with him.
只需这样做  他就会以为你对他有兴趣
That's all it'll take for him to think you're interested.
我假装喝醉了
I'll act good and drunk,
他就会以为我是个窝囊废  想要把你抢走
and he'll think I'm a loser and try to steal you away.
他会坚持到底
He will persist.
告诉他你不能离开我  现在还不行
Tell him you can't leave me. Not -- Not yet.
告诉他你打算趁我喝醉  偷我的钱包
Let him know you're trying to roll me.
他会想加入的
He'll want in.
他会帮你用酒灌醉我
He'll help you ply me with booze.
然后你就拿我的钱包  把我的卡偷走
Then you take my wallet. You lift the card.
懂了吗
Following this?
我们不是真的要付诸行动吧
We're not actually doing this, right?
我们只是说说而已吧
We're just talking?
是啊
Yeah.
只是说说而已
Just talkin'.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
才不是没什么
It's not nothing.
-怎么了  -我一直在想
- What? - ‭I keep thinking...
当时有没有另一种办法
was there another way?
什么另一种办法
Another way?
和查克吗  你是指那件事吗
W-- Chuck? Is that what you're talking about?
金  他把我们逼到了绝路
Kim...he had us in a corner, okay?
我们只能那样做
We did what we had to do.
可是丽贝卡...
But Rebecca...
发生的这一切都是他的错
Everything that happened was his own fault.
全都是
Everything.
你不要再回想他的事
You put him in the rearview mirror.
他不配占据你的思想
He is not worth thinkin' about.
结束了
Done.
谢谢
Why, thank you.
祝您今晚愉快
Have a good evening.
那个怎么样
How about that one?
我打赌我们能让他
I bet we could get him to...
投资吉赛尔·圣·克莱尔在南非的一些地
invest in some of Giselle St. Claire's land in South Africa.
没错
Oh, yeah.
绝对可以
Definitely.
那些采矿权都能归他所有
The mining rights would be all his.
不是吧
Really?
他打电话给我了
He called me.
原因很明显
For obvious reasons.
我不是来骗他的
Look, I'm not here to rip him off.
他把东西带来了吧
He has the stuff, right?
我要知道你的计划
I need to know what you're planning.
这跟你有什么关系
What's it matter to you?
我知道这是为塞拉曼加准备的
I know they're for Salamanca.
硝化甘油药丸
Nitro pills.
你老板心脏有问题
Your boss has heart problems.
你都已经猜到了
You already got it all figured out,
为什么还要问
why're you asking?
你打算怎么换药
How you gonna make the switch?
赫克托把药放在外套口袋里
Hector keeps the pills in his coat pocket.
他把外套挂起来时  我就趁机把药换掉
When he hangs up his coat, I'll make the switch.
他倒下了  然后呢
He goes down. Then what?
他心跳停止  这样就行了
His heart goes out. That's it.
很多人对塞拉曼加虎视眈眈
A lot of eyes on Salamanca.
如果你做了  怎么才能不让他们
You do this, ‭how are you gonna stop them
发现是你干的
from finding out it was you?
你是想让我不要这么做吗
Are you tryin' to tell me not to do this?
我什么也没说
I'm not tellin' you anything.
只是想确保你知道自己将要面对什么
Just want to make sure you know what you're getting into.
我没什么将要面对的
I'm not getting into anything.
我已身陷其中了
I'm in it.
我没办法
I've got no choice.
赫克托想利用我爸的生意
Hector wants to use my dad's business.
我爸是正直人
My dad is a straight arrow.
他不会同意的
He won't stand for it,
这意味着他会去找警察
which means he goes to the police,
也意味着他死定了
which means he's a dead man.
绝对不能这样
And that's not happening.
如果你被抓了  事情会变得更棘手
You get caught, it could get worse.
你以为我不知道在和谁打交道吗
You don't think ‭I know who I'm dealing with?
是的
No.
你不知道
I don't.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
还有比塞拉曼加更需要提防的人
There are more people than the Salamancas to worry about here.
如果你成功地
Now, if you manage to pull this off
把药片掉包了  而且还没被爆头
without a bullet in your head and switch those pills,
赶快把他们换回来
then switch 'em back.
换回来
Switch them back?
为什么
Why?
如果有人察觉药片不起作用了
Anyone gets an itch about the medicine not working,
就会检查药片
they're gonna look at those pills.
照我说的做
You do this...
把它们换回来
Switch 'em back.
那...
So...
你会让我们达成交易吗
you gonna let us make this deal?
你带钱了吗
You got the money?
很好
Good.
在交易之前...
Now, before we do this...
我还需要你一样东西
I'm gonna need one more thing from you.
圣罗萨保险集团
请讲
Yes?
好的
Okay.
瓦尔科女士可以见你了
Miss Valco will see you now.
第二扇门
‭Second door.
你好  请进
Hi there. Come on in.
好的
Yeah.
我给你们打过好几次电话
I called quite a few times
想解决一桩难题
about an issue I'm trying to address.
您记得保单号码吗
Do you have your policy number?
不记得
No.
你能查我的名字吗  麦吉尔
Can you just look up my name? McGill?
哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所的查尔斯·麦吉尔
Charles McGill ‭of Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill?
不  他是我哥哥
No, that's my brother.
我叫吉米
I'm Jimmy.
詹姆斯·麦吉尔  是个体律师
James McGill. Solo practitioner.
找到了
There you are.
上面显示您一年的费用都付好了
Looks like you're all paid up through the year.
这就是难题所在
That's sort of the issue.
我长话短说
Long story short,
经历了一系列不走运的事情
through a series of unfortunate events,
我的执照被吊销了
my license has been suspended.
是的  我看到了
Yes, I see that here.
没错  我在想你们是否可以把我停职
Right. Well, I was hoping I could get a refund
这段时间里的保险金额退给我
for the time ‭that I won't be a lawyer.
这样才公平  对吧
Now, that's only fair, right?
很抱歉  麦吉尔先生
I'm sorry, Mr. McGill.
这不符合规定
It doesn't work like that.
我们无法退还未使用的职业过失保险金
We don't refund for unused malpractice insurance.
但这么多钱不就打水漂了吗
But it's a -- ‭it's a lot of money for nothing.
我明白您的感受
I understand it seems that way,
但如果您的委托人之一
but if one of your clients
决定要对您提起诉讼
decides they want ‭to bring a suit against you,
这将划入保险范围
this continues your coverage.
问题就在这  我的委托人
That's the thing. My clients?
他们很爱我
They love me.
他们绝对不会起诉我
And they would never bring a suit against me.
我非常受人爱戴
I'm extremely lovable.
我能看出来
I can see that.
但这是公司规定
But it's company policy.
可不可以把保险金先闲置呢
What about ‭we put the insurance on hold?
在这之后  如果有人想起诉我
And then, if someone were to try to sue me --
虽然几率为零  但一旦发生
which they won't -- then we just, uh,
再按照保险合同办呢
kick that ol' policy back into gear?
我理解您的处境
I understand your situation.
真的
I do.
但公司有防止我们停止
But there are rules preventing us
或启动承保的明确规定
from stopping and starting coverage.
我很遗憾地告知您...
And I regret to inform you that...
当您明年重新复职的时候
when your license ‭is reinstated next year,
您的保险费
because of the suspension,
会受停职影响而...  上涨
your premiums are going to...go up.
且数目不小
Considerably.
此话怎讲
How considerably?
大约会涨...  150%
Looks like roughly... 150%.
我的天
God.
麦吉尔先生
Mr. McGill?
麦吉尔先生  我很抱歉
I... Mr. McGill, I'm sorry.
我们很希望能帮您  但心有余而力不足
I wish we could help you, but we just can't.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
太难了
It's hard.
真的太难了
Very, very hard.
我最近过得很艰苦
I'm just having a rough time.
我想休息一下
I just need a break.
就一下
Just one break.
我明白  我知道你无能为力  但...
And I know you -- I know you can't do anything, but...
我为了做社区服务精疲力竭
I'm getting run out on this community service and...
惨遭蹂躏和剥削  而且...
getting ripped off left and right, and...
我的车也坏了
my car won't start.
我的女朋友对我很失望  我的哥哥...
My gal is disappointed in me, and my brother...
我的哥哥病了
My brother is sick!
而且他孤家寡人一个
And he's alone.
我照顾了他那么多年
I spent years caring for him,
他现在却和我反目成仇
and now he hates me.
他是我唯一在世的亲人  他却恨我
He's the only family I got left, and he hates me.
恨得咬牙切齿
He hates my guts.
查尔斯就是你的哥哥吗
Is this your brother, Charles?
我假装不在乎  但他毕竟是我亲哥
And I pretend not to care, but he's my brother.
我怎么能不在乎
How can I not?
他得了精神病
He's mentally ill.
他把自己藏在一间没有电力的房子里
He's -- He's holed up in a house with no electricity.
他靠无铅汽油灯来过活
He's working ‭by the light of gas lanterns.
什么...
Wha--
替委托人打官司的时候屡屡犯错
He's making mistakes with his clients.
还在重要的文件上乱动手脚
He's mixin' up numbers on important documents.
他...  他在听证会上彻底地
He -- He -- He had ‭a complete mental breakdown
精神崩溃了
at the bar hearing.
你哥哥...  在法庭上崩溃了
Your brother -- ‭he had a breakdown in court?
都写在法庭记录里
It's in the transcripts.
天
God.
我很担心  我...
And I'm worried, I'm just --
如果他再搞砸一个重要委托人的案子...
If he screws up ‭with one more big client...
将会毁了他的
it's just gonna destroy him!
别...  别写...
Oh, don't -- don't write --
你在写什么  别  别写了
What are you writing? No, don't write.
我不是有意要那么说的
I-I didn't mean to say that.
我不想让他因为我而给你们
I don't want him ‭to get in trouble with you guys
-惹麻烦  -是的
- 'cause of me. I -- - ‭Right.
很抱歉  我现在就走
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go.
你不会干任何事情对吧
You're not gonna do anything, are you?
换做我我就不担心  麦吉尔先生
I-I wouldn't worry about it, Mr. McGill.
请振作起来
Uh, please feel better.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你别往心里去
Just for-- uh, forget.